A Guide to the Richmond Friends Meeting Records, 1849-2004
Library of Virginia
- Committee Files (Box 3-6, Reel 4668-4681)
  - Peace Education (Box 5, Reel 4674-4675)
    Consists of correspondence, minutes, reports, and publications focusing on the committee's responsibility to foster a greater understanding of peace among meeting members. Includes files on conscientious objectors, selective service, military tax withholding, Friends Committee on National Legislation, Friends World Committee, International Women's Friendship Conference for World Peace, UNESCO, and Vietnam. Of note are files relating to the Richmond Friends' efforts against a proposal to establish a military school within the Richmond public school system.
    - Call to Peacemaking (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Clerk Responsibilities (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Memos, 1989-1995, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "Fear God & Honor the Emperor: A Manual on Military Tax Withholding for Religious Employers" (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "For the Fun of It! Selected Cooperative Games for Children and Adults" (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Friends Committee on National Legislation (FCNL) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Friends World Committee (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - International Women's Friendship Conference for World Peace (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Membership List, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, Nov. 1987 - Apr. 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, Feb. 1990 - July 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, Jan. 1994 - Dec. 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, Jan. - June 1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, Feb. 1997 - Nov. 1998 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Mission Statement (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Peacemaking as a way of life (I-II) (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
    - Peace Testimony - Conscientious Objectors (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Press Releases and "Power of Place" submissions for Friends Newsletter, July 1997 - Jan. 1998, Aug. 1998, Nov. 1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Reports on Events, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Richmond Public Military School (I-III) (Box 5, Folder 21-23)
    - "Sanctuary For Refugees from El Salvador and Guatemala: A Resource Guide for Friends" (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Selective Service (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - UNESCO (United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization) (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Vietnam (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Yearly Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Religious Education (Box 5-6, Reel 4676-4680)
    This series includes bibliographies, correspondence, curriculum resources, financial records, memos, minutes, newsletters, publications, and reports that document the activities of the committee responsible for organizing religious education among the meeting's members. Also includes information on First Day Schools, committee files of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting Religious Education Committee, such as annual reports, financial records, mailing lists, and minutes, and copies of the Quaker publications, Interchange and The Quaking Post.
    - Adult Religious Education Advice and Materials (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Adult Religious Education Curricula (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Baltimore Yearly Meeting Religious Education Committee (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Baltimore Yearly Meeting Religious Education Committee Annual Report, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Baltimore Yearly Meeting Religious Education Committee Monthly Meeting Religious Education Annual Reports for 1989 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Baltimore Yearly Meeting Religious Education Committee Finances, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Baltimore Yearly Meeting Religious Education Committee Mailing Lists, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Baltimore Yearly Meeting Religious Education Committee Minutes of Meetings, Apr. 1991, Oct. 1992 - Aug. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Bible Readiness Faith Development (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Bibliographies (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Budget Expenses (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Business Meeting Workshop (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Catalogs (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Catoctin Quaker Camp (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Children (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Children and Home Queries and Advice (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Children and Meeting Community (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Children's Creative Response to Conflict (CCRC) (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Christmas (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Christmas Program, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Christmas - "Unplug the Christmas Machine" (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Class Lists, Notes, Letters (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Classroom Management (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Committee Instructions and Notes, 1990-1995 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence with Committee Members, 1987, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence with Frank Massey, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence with Marsha Holliday re. Junior Friends, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence with Other Baltimore Yearly Meeting Committees, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence with Other Monthly Meetings, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Creative Conflict Resolution Training (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Curricula Bibliography Project (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Curriculum (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Curriculum Catalogs (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Curriculum Information (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Curriculum Resources (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Educational Funding Resource Committee (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Empowering Children, Friends General Conference Focus Page (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Ethel Reynolds Fund Committee (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Finances (Expenses, Receipts, Records), 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - First Day Schools Activity Ideas and Monthly Queries (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - First Day Schools - Classroom Organization and Structures (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - First Day Schools - "Let Your Spirit Speak" (1988) (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - First Day Schools - Organizing a First Day School Workshop (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Friends General Conference Advance Program, June 28 - July 5, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Friends General Conference Religious Education Committee Communications Project, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Friends General Conference Religious Education Committee - Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, and Mailing Lists, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - General Program Activity Ideas (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Junior High Materials (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Junior Meeting for Worship and Business (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Intergeneration Queries - Value Clarification and Opening Doors to Religious Education (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Interchange (Quarterly Publication of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting), May 1992 - Sept. 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Minutes and Clerk Notes, Feb. 1992 - Dec. 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Minutes and Clerk Notes, Jan. 1996 - Feb. 1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Parent Orientation (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Pendle Hill Conferences and Retreats, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Publications and Catalogs (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Religious Education Ad Hoc (1996) and Resource Committee (1997) Notes (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Religious Education Newsletters ( Friends Witness, Christian Education Newsletter of New England Yearly Meeting of Friends ) (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Religious Education Resource Coordinator - Anne McKeithen Correspondence, May 1989 - Feb. 1991 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Religious Education Resource Coordinator - Visitation Evaluation Forms (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Reports, 1987-1998 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Resources for Quaker Parents and First Day School Teacher (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Resource Lists (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Quaker Associations Pamphlets (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Quaker Parenting Workshop Materials (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - The Quaking Post, 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Stewardship (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Subcommittee on Religious Education, Richmond Friends Meeting, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Summer Program (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Wider Quaker Fellowship (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Workshop Organization (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Spring Retreat (Box 6, Reel 4681)
    Includes announcements, correspondence, reports, and schedules concerning the Spring Retreats held at the Clearing from 1978 to 2000.
    - Spring Retreats, 1978-1979, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Spring Retreats, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Spring Retreats, 1993-1998, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - SRC Manual (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Trustees (Box 6, Reel 4681)
    The Trustees' files concern gift policy, insurance, the safe-deposit box, burial space for Ava Fish Frazer, the widow of Emmet Manley Frazer, and include meeting notes from June 1992, March 1994, and April 1995.
    - Gift Policy - Policies, Minutes, Notes, and Correspondence, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Gift Policy - Correspondence, July - Aug. 1993 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Insurance (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Letter to Hollywood Cemetery Company re. the reservation of burial space for Ava Fish Frazer, the widow of Emmet Manley Frazer, 12 Dec. 1962 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Meeting Notes, 7 June 1992, 16 Mar. 1994, 25 Apr. 1995 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Safe Deposit Box (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Membership Records, 1849-1998 (Box 6-7, Reel 4682-4684)
  This series includes annual reports of membership statistics (1982-1987), guest registers (1953-1991), membership register (1849-1997), membership cards, seeker's packets, Richmond meeting directories (1956, 1974-1998), Baltimore Yearly Meeting directories, correspondence of the meeting recorder regarding membership, memorials, and lists of committee members (1957-1958, 1964-1966, 1975-1987), members withdrawn, meeting children, and Midlothian and Williamsburg transfers. The earliest date in the membership register, 1849-1997, represents the birth year of one of the members. Also includes files on the following individual members: Seth Arginteanu and Emmett Shorter. Of interest is files of the Talent Resource Book, compiled by the meeting's 3rd-5th graders and describing the talents and interests of the member of the Richmond Friends Meeting.
  - Annual Reports of Membership Statistics, 1968, 1972, 1974-1981 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Annual Reports of Membership Statistics, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Annual Reports of Membership Statistics, 1988-1997 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Arginteanu, Seth (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Baltimore Yearly Meeting Directory (Homewood), Feb. 1941 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Baltimore Yearly Meeting Directory (Homewood), Nov. 1950 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Change Log (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Committees and Assignments, 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Committee Membership, 1957-1958, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Committee Membership, 1975-1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence of Meeting Recorder re. Membership, 1958-1966 (bulk 1961-1962) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence of Meeting Recorder re. Membership, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Guest Register, 7 June 1953 - 18 Sept. 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Guest Register, 6 Nov. 1966 - 28 May 1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Guest Register, 18 June 1978 - 6 Jan. 1991
  - Meeting Children (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Directory, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Directories, 1974-1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Meeting Directories, 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Meeting Directories, 1993-1994, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Membership Cards (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Membership Register, 1849-1997
  - Membership Requests (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Members of Richmond Friends Meeting as of December 1995, A-C (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Members of Richmond Friends Meeting as of December 1995, D-H (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Members of Richmond Friends Meeting as of December 1995, J-P (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Members of Richmond Friends Meeting as of December 1995, R-Z (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Members Withdrawn Through Choice, Transfer, Death as of December 1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Memorials (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Notes Concerning Meeting Members and Regular Attenders (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Seeker's Packet, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Seeker's Packet, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Seeker's Packet - Originals (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Shorter, Emmett (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Talent Resource Book, A-L (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Talent Resource Book, M-Y (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Williamsburg Transfer, 1982-1986 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Midlothian Transfer, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Newsletters, 1956-2001 (Box 7-8, Reel 4685-4688)
  These newsletters include schedules of events, business meeting news, committee news, budget information, announcements, and member notes.
  - 1956-1960 (bulk 1958) (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Apr. 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - 1983 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - 1984 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - 1985 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - 1986 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - 1987 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 1988 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Jan. - June 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - July - Dec. 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Jan. - June 1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - July - Dec. 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- American Friends Service Committee (Box 8, Reel 4688)
  This series includes material relating to the American Friends Service Committee, a Quaker organization established in 1917 to provide conscientious objectors with an opportunity to help civilian war victims. Consists of 50th anniversary publications, 1963 and 2002 annual reports, information on the Algerian relief program, Life Over Debt Campaign, and recovery kits for Kosovo refugees, and a copy of the Winter 2004 edition of Quaker Action, a publication of the American Friends Service Committee.
  - 50th Anniversary Publications (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1963 Report (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Algerian Relief Program (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Life Over Debt Campaign (part of the Africa Initiative) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Recovery Kits for Kosovo Refugees (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Quaker Action, vol. 85 no. 1 (Winter 2004) (Box 8, Folder 22)
- War Tax Resistance (Box 8, Reel 4689)
  Consists of correspondence, brochures, newsletters, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, publications, and resource packets relating to efforts among the peace churches (Friends, Brethren, and Mennonites) to stop paying taxes that support war and establish a World Peace Tax Fund. Includes files on National Council for World Peace Tax Fund, Peace Tax Fund legislation, the Richmond Peace Education Center.
  - Affirm Life: Pay for Peace (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Clippings, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Conscience and Military Tax Campaign (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - National Council for a World Peace Tax Fund (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Pamphlets and Brochures (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Peace Tax Fund Bill, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Peace Tax Fund Bill - "Handbook on Military Taxes & Conscience" (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Publications (I-II) (Box 8, Folder 30-31)
  - Resources Packet on War Taxes (Taskforce on War Taxes, Baltimore Yearly Meeting, Religious Society of Friends) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Richmond Peace Education Center (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Virginia Quarterly Meeting 1961-1975 (Box 8, Reel 4690)
  Includes records of the Virginia Quarterly Meeting, including attendance lists, correspondence, minutes of the Executive Committee, September 1962-October 1968, newsletters, newspaper clippings, programs, and schedules of events. Also includes files concerning the transfer of the Black Creek Monthly Meeting to the Corinth and Somerton Monthly Meetings and the disposition of the property of the Black Creek Monthly Meeting.
  - 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - 1970-1979 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Black Creek Monthly Meeting - Transfer to Corinth and Somerton Monthly Meetings and Concern About Property, 1965-1968, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee, Sept. 1962 - Oct. 1968 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Representative Meeting, 25 Oct. 1997 (Box 8, Reel 4690)
  This series consists of the agenda and minutes from the 25 October 1997 Representative Meeting. This meeting involved representatives from twenty-six monthly meetings comprising the Baltimore Yearly Meeting.
  - Agenda and Minutes, 25 Oct. 1997 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Ashland Friends Meeting 1991-1999 (Box 8, Reel 4690)
  Includes business meeting minutes, October 1991-June 1999,of the Ashland Indulged Meeting. These minutes contains lists of members present for meetings, announcements, financial reports, and committee reports.
  - Business Meeting Minutes, Oct. 1991 - Nov. 1995 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Business Meeting Minutes, Mar. 1996 - June 1998, June 1999 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Midlothian Friends Meeting, 1988-1995 (Box 9, Reel 4691)
  Includes brochures, business meeting minutes, 1989, 1991-1995, membership records, financial reports, reports, newsletters, and spiritual state of the meeting reports, 1990-1995, of the Midlothian Friends Meeting, now a full-fledged meeting.
  - Brochures (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Business Meeting Minutes, May 1989, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Business Meeting Minutes, 1994 - Apr. 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Care and Counsel Committee and Spiritual Nurture Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Committees and Positions, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Financial Reports, Apr. 1991-1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Status, 1988-1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Membership Lists, 1989/90, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, 30 Sept. 1989 - Feb. 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Dec. 1988, Apr. 1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Religious Education Committee (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Spiritual State of Meeting Reports, 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Publications (Box 9-10)
  Includes annual reports of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting (1977-1980, 1984-1985, 1987), Baltimore Yearly Meeting Faith and Practice Manual (1988), elders handbook, invitations to worship, songbooks, and copies of Fellowship (March 1990, April/May 1990), The Friend A Religious and Literary Journal (September 1848-September 1849), Friends Journal (February 1986-July 1990), Friends United Press Pamphlet Series, the Monthly Newsletter from the 57th Street Meeting of Friends (1969-1975), minutes, proceedings and yearbooks of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting (1929-2002), proceedings of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends at Park Avenue (1930), proceedings of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends at Stony Run (1959-1966), and proceedings of the Philadelphia Yearly Meeting (1958). Also includes miscellaneous newsletters such as the Dharma Wheel, Friends for Lesbian and Gay Concerns, Information Express, Right Sharing of World Resources, and TeenQuake, and miscellaneous pamphlets and brochures relating to conferences, workshops, and spirituality and worship. THIS SERIES IS NOT AVAILABLE ON MICROFILM.
  - Advance and Annual Reports, Baltimore Yearly Meeting of the Religious Society of Friends, 1977-1980, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Baltimore Yearly Meeting Faith and Practice (1988) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Elders Handbooks (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Fellowship, Mar. 1990, Apr./May 1990 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - The Friend. A Religious and Literary Journal, Volume XXII (Sept. 1948 - Sept. 1849)
  - Friends Journal, 15 Feb. 1986, 1 Mar. 1986, 1 Apr. 1986, 15 Apr. 1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Friends Journal, 1/15 June 1986, 1/15 Sept. 1986, 15 Dec. 1986, 1 Feb. 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Friends Journal, 1/15 June 1987, 1/15 Aug. 1987, Oct. 1987, Nov. 1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Friends Journal, Jan. 1988, June 1988, Aug. 1988, Sept. 1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Friends Journal, Nov. 1988, Dec. 1988, Feb. 1989, Mar. 1989 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Friends Journal, Apr. 1990, May 1990, June 1990, July 1990 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Friends United Press Pamphlet Series (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Invitations to Worship (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Lists of Books (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Monthly Newsletters from the 57th Street Meeting of Friends, Oct. 1969, Feb. 1972, July/Aug. 1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Songbooks (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Newsletters (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets and Brochures (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Minutes of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1929-1932 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Minutes of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1933, 1936-1938 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Minutes of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1939-1942 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Minutes of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1943-1947 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1948-1950, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1953, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Minutes of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1958-1961 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Minutes of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Minutes of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Proceedings of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Proceedings of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Proceedings of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Yearbook of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Yearbook of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Yearbook of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Yearbook of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Yearbook of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Yearbook of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Proceedings of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, Park Avenue, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Proceedings of the Baltimore Yearly Meeting of Friends, Stony Run, 1959, 1961, 1962, 1963, 1965, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Proceedings of the Philadelphia Yearly Meeting, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 20)